<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fit</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="arnold_shoulder_press">Sit on an exercise bench with back support and hold two dumbbells in front of you at about upper chest level with your palms facing your body and your elbows bent. Tip: Your arms should be next to your torso. The starting position should look like the contracted portion of a dumbbell curl.Now to perform the movement, raise the dumbbells as you rotate the palms of your hands until they are facing forward.Continue lifting the dumbbells until your arms are extended above you in straight arm position. Breathe out as you perform this portion of the movement.After a second pause at the top, begin to lower the dumbbells to the original position by rotating the palms of your hands towards you. Tip: The left arm will be rotated in a counter clockwise manner while the right one will be rotated clockwise. Breathe in as you perform this portion of the movement.</string>
    <string name="arnold_short">Main Muscle: Shoulders</string>
    <string name="burpee_text">Bend over or squat down and place your hands on the floor in front of you, just outside of your feet.Jump both feet back so that you’re now in plank position.Drop to a push-up—your chest should touch the floor. You can also drop to your knees here, which makes the impending push-up easier.Push up to return to plank position (this can be a strict push-up, a push-up from the knees, or not a push-up at all (i.e., just push yourself up from the ground as you would if you weren’t working out)—your choice).Jump the feet back in toward the hands.Explosively jump into the air, reaching your arms straight overhead.</string>
    <string name="burpee_short">Main Muscle: All body parts</string>
    <string name="bent_press_text">Clean a kettlebell to your shoulder. Clean the kettlebell to your shoulders by extending through the legs and hips as you raise the kettlebell towards your shoulder. The wrist should rotate as you do so. This will be your starting position.Begin my leaning to the side opposite the kettlebell, continuing until you are able to touch the ground with your free hand, keeping your eyes on the kettlebell. As you do so, press the weight vertically be extending through the elbow, keeping your arm perpendicular to the ground.Return to an upright position, with the kettlebell above your head. Return the kettlebell to the shoulder and repeat for the desired number of repetitions.</string>
    <string name="bent_press_short">Main Muscle: Abdominals</string>
    <string name="external_rotation_text">Lie sideways on a flat bench with one arm holding a dumbbell and the other hand on top of the bench folded so that you can rest your head on it.Bend the elbows of the arm holding the dumbbell so that it creates a 90-degree angle between the upper arm and the forearm. Tip: Keep the arm parallel to your torso.Now bend the elbow while keeping the upper arm stationary. In this manner, the forearm will be parallel to the floor and perpendicular to your torso (Tip: So the forearm will be directly in front of you). The upper arm will be stationary by your torso and should be parallel to the floor (aligned with your torso at all times). This will be your starting position.As you breathe out, externally rotate your forearm so that the dumbbell is lifted up in a semicircle motion as you maintain the 90 degree angle bend between the upper arms and the forearm. You will continue this external rotation until the forearm is perpendicular to the floor and the torso pointing towards the ceiling. At this point you will hold the contraction for a second.As you breathe in, slowly go back to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="external_rotation_short">Main Muscle: Shoulders</string>
    <string name="advanced_gladiator_press"> To do this press, set up in a side-plank position with a kettlebell (or dumbbell) in your free hand. “Rack” the kettlebell at your shoulder, then press it up to form a straight line with your supporting arm.If you can, raise your free leg and keep it there for the duration of the set. If you find it very difficult to keep this position, it’s a sign of muscle weakness and/or muscle imbalances that need to be addressed.Before you begin the press, pull both shoulders back and down—referred to as “packing the shoulders.” this will keep the shoulders safe and create more tension, which will provide a more stable base and more strength for the press.</string>
    <string name="advanced_gladiator_press_short">>Main Muscle: All body parts</string>
    <string name="squat">Stand with your feet just over shoulder width apart.Keep your back in a neutral position, and keep your knees centered over your feet.Slowly bend your knees, hips and ankles, lowering until you reach a 90-degree angle.Return to starting position .</string>
    <string name="bulgarian_squat">Hold a dumbbell in each hand with your arms fully extended at your sides and your palms facing each other. With your feet hip-width apart, place the instep of your rear foot on a bench. Your feet should be approximately three feet apart.Lower your hips toward the floor so that your rear knee comes close to the floor. Pause and drive through your front heel to return to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="swimming">The Freestyle Stroke or front crawl is often the preferred stroke of seasoned swimmers. It uses alternating arm movements with an above water recovery. The legs execute a flutter kick.Breaststroke is the most popular swim stroke of all. In breaststroke, both arms execute half-circular arm movements at the same time under water in front of the swimmer. The arm recovery also occurs under water. The legs simultaneously execute a whip kick.The butterfly stroke stands out among the competitive strokes because of it’s unique and spectacular technique. It uses a symmetrical arm stroke with an above water recovery. It also uses a wave-like body undulation and a dolphin kick.As its name suggests, backstroke is swum on the back. It uses alternating circular arm movements and an above water recovery. The legs execute a flutter kick similar to the one used in freestyle.The sidestroke is an old swim stroke swum on the side that uses a scissor kick and asymmetrical under water arm movements.</string>
</resources>
